

#### **PROFILE**

Helvin Rymer is a rookie freelance web designer, developing sites as of 2019. Studying Computer Information System, and following up with studies in Web Development with a focus on Bash, HTML5, JQuery and CSS.

Prior to Web Development, Mr. Rymer has had experience working in real estate as a salesperson and managing his own social media presence successfully. He has earned leadership awards in his previous position and has proven to be someone who shows great pride and professionalism in his work.

#### CONTACT

PHONE: (929)523-6682

WEBSITE: HelvinRymer.com

EMAIL: Helvin159@gmail.com

# **HOBBIES**

Music Sports Politics

# HELVIN RYMER

# Front End Developer

#### **EDUCATION**

### New York City College of Technology

September, 2019 - Present

Full Stack Development Course. I was assigned to develop multiple websites, both static and dynamic. I worked with multiple languages including HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and MySQL. I finished at the top of my class.

### The High School for Excellence

Graduation - 2007

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Keller Williams NYC - Senior Real Estate Salesperson

February, 2016 - March, 2019

My responsibilities at Keller Williams were to work in a team environment to acquire new clients, maintain relationships with current clients and manage & prepare marketing for live listings. I was also responsible for marketing via social media, email marketing, telemarketing, etc. I received an award for my role in team leadership during my time at Keller Williams.

## The Hecht Group - Senior Real Estate Salesperson

November, 2014 - January, 2016

My responsibilities at the Hecht Group included marketing via social media and real estate channels such as Trulia.

#### Anchor Associates - Real Estate Salesperson

May, 2012 - October, 2014

My responsibilities at Anchor Associates included marketing and lead generation.

### **SKILLS**

